Register of the Frances E. Willis Papers, 1906-1983.
Hoover Institution Archives
- PHOTOGRAPHS, 1916-1979.
  - 1 print of Francis Willis in Norway; 1 print of Frances Willis and others in Norway, 1957., undated (Folder V)
  - 12 prints of an American Embassy party; 16 prints of Frances Willis and others., 1958 (Folder W)
  - 1 print of Frances Willis; 2 prints of Frances Willis and her mother; 4 prints of an Embassy Christmas party; 2 prints of the Embassy interior. 3 prints of Frances Willis and others; 5 prints of Frances Willis, Dr. Ralph J. Bunche, Under Secretary of the United Nations on his visit to Norway, 1958; 1 outdoor scene. (Folder X)
  - 22 prints of a wreath-laying ceremony, 1959; 5 prints of a NIKE missile ceremony; 14 prints of Frances Willis and Norwegian fisherman; 1959. (Folder Y)
  - 36 prints of Frances Willis and others, Norway., 1959 (Folder Z)
  - 6 prints of Frances Willis, Louis Armstrong on his visit to Norway; 2 prints of Frances Willis and others, Norway., 1959 (Folder AA)
  - 3 prints of Frances Willis at the Indian Embassy, Oslo, January 1960; 11 prints of the visit of Admiral Burke, May, 1960; 1 print of Frances Willis and others at a conference in Paris, May, 1960; 3 prints of Francis Willis and others; 6 prints of Frances Willis United Nations publicity photos; 4 prints of Frances Willis and others at the United nations; 6 prints of Frances Willis and others, 1960; 4 prints of Francis Willis and others, circa 1960. (Folder AB)
  - 1 print of Frances Willis and others, Norway; 12 prints of Frances Willis' swearing-in ceremony as Ambassador to Sri Lanka; 2 prints of Frances Willis and Dean Rusk; 33 prints of Frances Willis and others at various ceremonial gatherings in Sri Lanka; 3 prints of Frances Willis in Honolulu; 2 prints of Frances Willis and Mrs. Bandaranike, Prime Minister of Sri Lanka., 1961 (Folder AC)
  - 7 prints of Frances Willis; 8 prints of Frances Willis and others at Career Service Awards ceremony; 5 prints of Frances Willis and others as she took oath as Career Ambassador; 30 prints of Frances Willis and others at various ceremonial and social functions in Sri Lanka; 1 print of Frances Willis and Mrs. Bandaranike, Prime Minister of Sri Lanka, 1 print of U.S.S. Power; 1 outdoor scene., 1962 (Folder AD)
  - 37 prints of Frances Willis and others, 1 print of Frances Willis, 2 unidentified prints, 1 print of the American Embassy, (?) Colombo, Sri Lanka/, circa 1962 (Folder AE)
  - 2 prints of Frances Willis and others on the U.S.S. Owens, 4 prints of Frances Willis and others at the Marine Ball; 3 prints of Frances Willis and others on the U.S.S. Lloyd Thomas; 17 prints of Frances Willis and others, 2 unidentified prints; 4 prints of Frances Willis and others on her travels in Sri Lanka, 1963. (Folder AF)
  - 6 prints of Frances Willis and Dean Rusk at her retirement ceremony. 7 prints of Frances Willis and W. Averell Harriman at her retirement ceremony; 1 print of Frances Willis and LaRue R. Lutkins., 1964 (Folder mAG)
  - 30 prints of Frances Willis and others at her birthday party, May 20, 1964; 9 prints of Frances Willis and others, 24 prints of Frances Willis and others on her visit to Kandy, Sri Lanka; 4 prints of Frances Willis and others on her visit to Alutnuwara, Sri Lanka, January, 1964; 6 prints of Frances Willis and others at her farewell dinner, Colombo, September 1964. (Folder AI)
  - 3 prints of Frances Willis and others; 1 print of Frances Willis; 3 prints of Frances Willis and others, United Nations, 1965. (Folder AJ)
  - 1 print of Frances Willis and other, 1966; 3 prints of Francis Willis; 4 prints of Frances Willis and others, 1967; 2 prints of Frances Willis; 2 prints of Frances Willis and others, 1968; 1 print of Frances Willis and others, 1970. (Folder AK)
  - 6 prints of Frances Willis, George F. Kennan, and others at Foreign Service Day honoring Willis and Kennan, November, 1973; 3 prints of Frances Willis and others; 2 prints of Frances Willis, 1974; 1 print of Frances Willis and others, 1978; 6 scenic postal cards; 8 slides; 18 negatives. (Folder AL)